hi my name is
i received an email from icsa
from a lady by name sneha saying that
please renew my car policy
i did renew my car policy
and once the renew my car policy is done
i was given a link to go ahead and click
for uh to see
go to my dashboard to see my policy once
i clicked on dashboard
i very funnily enter into this portal
where all the policies
renewed by this employee of isis lombard
are being listed straight forward here
complete policies that this person has
done first all the payments that are
done or failed the personal details of
the employee
like date of birth address etc
and all the saved codes now let's come
to the policy section
and see you see any of those policies
i can click and open the policy
and i will be able to
basically see the policy completely and
i get all the details
okay i was able to download all the
policies
i hope you're able to see my screen
all the policies are directly clickable
viewable
by me i can see all the policies this
lady has renewed
this is such a breach of personal data
where isis or lombard is so reckless in
building such kind of websites
this kind of things have to be done very
strictly
and you know there should be action
taken account against these kind of
companies